M FAJRI HUSAINI

6282287656102 | https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammad-fajri-husaini-716741215 | mfajrihusaini05@gmail.com | Tomang, Jakarta Barat

PROFILE

I am a tech-enthusiastic Frontend and Mobile Developer, with a passion for creating outstanding technology solutions. With expertise in developing efficient website flows and creating engaging and user-friendly mobile applications, I have contributed to various projects that combine innovation with quality.

EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer, Fulltime

Skyworx Indonesia | Jakarta Pusat

Mei 2023 – Present

- Design and develop websites using VueJS dan PostgreSQL
- Develop mobile apps using flutter framework
- Using a VCS (Version Control System) like GitLab and GitHub as a connector between developers

Multiplatform and Back End, Internship

Dicoding Indonesia | Remote (Independent Campus)

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022

- Learn basic programming logic
- Designed UI/UX Design about coffee ordering application
- Design and develop projects from basic, intermediate and expert using flutter framework
- Designing and developing simple API back-end systems with JavaScript
- Learn the basics of AWS cloud computing

Mobile Developer, Internship

Seven Inc | Yogyakarta

Aug 2021 – Jan 2022

- Slicing responsive user interface using flutter
- Building a system that connects with firebase services and MySQL database
- Hosting Rest API using Heroku platform

EDUCATION

Diploma in Computer Engineering | 3.63/4.00 GPA

Padang State Polytechnic | Padang

2019 - 2022

Learning algorithms along with web-based programming and mobile applications

Natural Sciences | 89/100 GPA

One Senior High School | Rengat

2016 - 2019

• Studying lessons related to the field of computers and mathematic

SKILLS

- Soft Skill: Teamwork, Individual Work
- Hard Skill: Flutter, VueJS, CodeIgniter, PostgreSQL, MySQL, Firebase, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Laravel
- Software Skill: Visual Studio Code, Database Client, Git